TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
좋아, 가자, 블랙메일!
Alright! Let's do this, Blackmail!
우리도 가자, 롤스타!
Let's do this too, Rollstar!
돈 드라큘리오, 엄호 부탁해!
Don Draculio, cover us!
DDK형 돈 드라큘리오
DDK Type Don Draculio
응!
Yeah!
페이저 발사!
Phaser, fire!
롤스타! 더 가까이 다가가서 쏴!
Rollstar! Approach more and shoot!
블랙메일, 뒤로 돌아가! 더 간격을 벌려!
Blackmail, go to back and keep distance!
지금이야, 닌닌자!
Now, Ninninja!
뭐해, 돈 드라큘리오?!
What are you doing, Don Draculio?!
가, 돈 드라큘리오!
Go, Don Draculio!
예!
Yessir!
돈 도라큐리오, 오, 오른쪽이야!
Don Draculio, r- right!
예, 마스터!
Yessir, Master!
아니, 왼쪽이야!
No, left!
잠깐...
Wait...
데빌 해머!
Devil Hammer!
돈 드라큘리오, 위에서 온다!
Don Draculio, incoming from upward!
승부 났네.
Match set.
약한 놈하고 팀을 짜면 안 돼.
That's why you shouldn't team up with weak ones.
대체! 움직임이 느려서 지루해!
Really! His movement is slow and that's boring!
정말, 정말!
Really, really!
저기, 이 메달 네 거야?
Hey, is this medal yours?
응.
Yeah.
안 됐네.
Too bad.
어쩔 수 없었어. 내가 약하니까 그런 거야.
It couldn't be helped. It's because I'm weak.
어때, 지금 우리 집에 놀러오지 않을래?
Hey, would you like to come to my house to play?
네 집에?
Your house?
응. 네 돈 드라큘리오를 누구에게도 지지 않을 최고의 머신으로 만들어 줄게.
Yes. I will make your Don Draculio into the matchless machine that will defeat everybody else.
정말? 근데 왜...
Really? But why?
누구라도 지는 건 싫어해. 그러니까 누구에게도 지지 않는 머신으로 날뛰어 봐.
Nobody likes to lose. Why not try raging with a machine that will never be defeated?
괴담: 밤의 과학실
Ghost Story: Science Room in Night
(en: Robbed Zombies)
정말, 왜 이런 시간에 카가미야마의 인생 상담을 들어야 하는 거야?
Really? Why do I have to counsel Kagamiyama with his life this late?
그것도 이런 곳에서.
Moreover, why this place?
라고 불만이 몇개를 넘어가도 가만히 둘 수는 없는 부하 생각하는 두목이었습니다.
That's our boss, who can't leave her underlings alone, even when she doesn't want to!
흥, 그래도 왠지 기분 나쁘다. 밤의 학교라는 곳은.
Hmph. Anyway, it's unpleasant to be in school on a night.
그래요?
Do you think so?
그래. 난 이런 거 똑바로 말하면 별로야. 와 줘서 고마워, 페퍼캣.
Yes. To be honest, I don't like these things. Thank you for coming with me, Peppercat.
도움이 되어서 잘 되었어용!
Glad I could help, meow!
과학실
Science Room
카가미야마, 있냐?
Kagamiyama, are you there?
놀래키지 마라, 신체모형!
Don't surprise me like that, dummy!
아마 카가미야마 없는 것 같구나. 돌아가자, 페퍼캣.
Seems that there's no Kagamiyama here. Let's go back, Peppercat.
잘 왔어.
Welcome.
기다렸어.
I've been waiting.
저 목소리는 카가미야마가 아니군! 누구냐!
That voice isn't from Kagamiyama! Who's there?!
볼 일 있는 건 네가 아니야. 내가 보고 싶었던 건 거기 있는 페퍼캣 양.
I'm not interested in you. Who I wanted to see is Peppercat over there.
뭐?!
What?!
호오, 재미있군. 이 키쿠히메 님께 로보틀을 걸다니 좋은 배짱이야.
Interesting. You've got some guts, to ask for a Robattle to me, Kikuhime.
받아 주지! 가라, 페퍼캣!
I'll accept your challenge! Go, Peppercat!
페퍼캣!
Peppercat!
그러니까, 결국 얘 안 왔어.
And then, he eventually didn't come.
그러니까, 애초에 안 간다 했잖아?
You know that I told you I'm not going at the first place, right?
유령의 집이라고 말했을 땐 전혀 안 무섭다며. 다들 겁쟁이라고 니예니예 했잖아.
When I said we're going to haunted house, you said you weren't scared at all. Also you said everyone is coward!
그래서?
So what?
그럼 왜 안 온 거야?
Then why didn't you come?!
그러니까, 난 싫다니까! 유령이라던가 괴물이라던가 그런 거!
Again, I told you I don't like ghosts, monsters or things like that!
어, 무섭냐?
Oh, you're scared of them?
어, 그래. 난 유령이 싫어요. 이 세계에서 유령이 제일 무서워요.
Oh, sure, I hate ghosts. I'm scared of ghosts more than everything else in the whole wide world!
갑자기 정색했다!
He's serious!
저기, 저기, 저기! 다들 알아?
Hey, hey, hey! Did you know?
뭐야. 아침부터 꽥꽥 시끄럽게.
What is it? You're being noisy from morning!
뭐, 이야기라도 들어봐.
Well, just listen to my story.
뭔 사건이야?
Did some accident happen?
사건이라 하면 사건이네.
Well, you can say so.
뭐야, 그게?
What's that?
잠깐 비켜 봐. 그 이야기라는 게 말야, 최근 메다로트 사이에 묘한 병이 돌고 있대.
Excuse me. About that story: recently, some kind of disease is being contagious among Medarots.
뭐야, 그 병이라니?
And what is that disease exactly?
무엇보다도, 주변 도브로크 마을에서 온 것 같은데, 소문에 따르면 매 밤 메다로트를 공격하는 수수께끼의 괴물이 있어서
It seems that the disease came from neighboring Doburoku village.
Rumor says that there is a mysterious monster that attacks Medarots every night,
그 놈에게 당하면 병에 걸리는 것 같아.
and one will be infected when one loses to the monster .
에, 소름돋아!
That's scary!
내가 괴물 무서워하는 거 알고 있던 거지?!
You knew I am scared of monsters, right?!
들켰네.
You found out!
들키고 자시고 할 게 아니잖아.
I already knew that.
그래도, 앞으로의 이야기가 중요해. 그 병에 걸린 메다로트는 다들 급히 파워 다운되어버려 마치 좀비가 되어 버려.
But what's more important is that Medarots with that disease will lose power quickly and become zombie-like state.
게다가 좀비 상태가 된 메다로트는 마스터가 자고 있는 동안 매 밤 마을을 헤매어 상대 불문하고 로보틀을 건대!
Moreover, Medarots who have become zombie state will wander around the village and do Robattles, no matter who the opponent is,
during their masters are sleeping!
그럼 그 메다로트에 당한 상대는 또 좀비화되어 다음 사냥감을 노리고!
And then the ones who was taken down by that Medarot will be zombified and look for another prey!
그래! 바로 그거야!
Yes! That's right!
그, 그건 마치 흡혈귀 드라큘라하고 같은 이야기잖아요.
I- isn't that the exact same story with Dracula?
뭐, 그럴 수도 있는 거지!
Well, maybe that's right!
괴물이란 게,
Is that monster...
이런 거?
like this?
괜찮니, 잇키 군?
Are you okay, Ikki?
정말 겁쟁이네요.
He's really a coward!
그러니까 말했잖아!
Again, I told you!
어? 왜 그래, 키쿠히메?
Huh? What's wrong, Kikuhime?
두목, 아침부터 이상해요.
Boss, you're being weird from morning!
설마 네 페퍼캣도 이미 좀비화됐냐?
Could it be that your Peppercat is already zombified?
그런 거 아니야!
That's not it!
두, 두목?
B- boss?
페퍼캣.
Peppercat.
페퍼캣. 또 누굴 쫒았니?
Peppercat. Did you get someone again?
부탁이야! 빨리 원래의 너로 돌아와 줘! 페퍼캣!
Please! Become yourself again! Peppercat!
누구?
Who is this?
페퍼캣을 원래대로 되돌리고 싶으면 오늘 17시에 우리 집에 와.
If you want Peppercat to be normal, then come to my house at 17 o'clock.
젠장! 코쿠류 짓이었구나!
Damn it! Kokuryu did this!
텐료 잇키의 약점은 괴물이구나. 좋은 거 알려줘서 고마워.
So, Tenryo Ikki's weakness is monsters. Thank you for letting me know that.
잇키의 약점은 알려 주었으니까 어서 페퍼캣을 원래대로 돌려놔!
Now that I told you about Ikki's weakness, restore Peppercat!
음, 그 정보만으로는 부족해.
Hm, that information is not enough.
뭐?!
What?!
오늘밤 잇키를 쓰러트릴 거야. 넌 그걸 도와주길 부탁할게.
I'm going to take Ikki down today. I'd like to ask you to help me.
더, 더러워!
Y- you're dirty!
내 말 안 들을 거야?
Are you going to refuse that?
아, 아니...
No...
그럼 부탁할게.
Then, please do so.
젠장.
Damn.
도, 돌아가자. 난 이런 거 제일 싫다고 말했잖아.
L- let's go back. I told you I hate this very much!
뭔 소리야! 소문의 괴물이 학교 과학실에 실존한대!
What are you talking about?! They say that the rumored monster exists in the school science room!
대단한 특종 잡은 이상 이 아리카 님의 저널리스트 혼이 가만히 둘 수 없잖아?!
Now that I got an awesome scoop, Arika's journalist spirit can't let me stay back!
그래도 뭔가 나오면...
But what if something comes out?
괜찮아. 의지할 테니까.
It's alright. I'm depending on someone here.
아니, 그렇게까지 말해준다면야...
Well, if you say so...
때가 되면 메타비가 구해줄 테니까.
When the time comes, Metabee will rescue me.
그래!
Yeah!
진짜...
Really...
그래서 그 정보는 어디서 얻었어?
So, where did you get that information?
전화.
From a call.
전화? 누구한테서?
Call from who?
키쿠히메.
Kikuhime.
키쿠히메?! 왜 키쿠히메가 전화한 거야?!
Kikuhime?! Why would Kikuhime even call you?!
몰라! 본인한테 물어 봐!
I don't know! Ask her yourself!
대단해요, 두목! 겁쟁이 잇키를 밤의 학교에 불러내 놀래킬 작전이라니 왠지 엄청난 아이디어!
Awesome, boss! It's an awesome idea to call Ikki to the school in night when he's a coward!
정말 두근두근거려요!
I'm really looking forward for it!
난 놀러 온 게 아니야.
I'm not here to play.
아, 아무것도 아니야! 자, 거기서 꾸물대지 말고 작전 시작이다!
I- it's nothing! Don't stay there, and start the operation!
예!
Yessir!
기다려, 페퍼캣. 곧 건강하게 해 줄게.
Just you wait, Peppercat. I'll make you healthy soon.
뭔가 나올 거 같아.
Something's gonna pop out.
야, 잇키! 한심하다!
Hey, Ikki! You're pitiful!
그래, 정신 차려!
Yeah, get a grip!
그런 소릴 해도...
But still...
뭐, 뭐야! 놀랐잖아!
W- what was that for?! You surprised me!
우는 소리가... 아기 우는 소리가...
Someone's crying... some baby is crying...
기분 탓 아냐? 무서워, 무서워 하고 생각하니까 들리는 거야!
That's just you! You're hearing things because you're thinking that you're scared!
그런가...
I wonder...
가자.
Let's go.
고양이 울음소리. 고양이.
A cat cried. A cat...
작전 1 성공. 카가미야마, 실수하지 마.
Plan #1 successful. Kagamiyama, do not make a mistake.
예, 두목.
Yessir, boss.
아리카, 왠지 기분 나빠.
Arkia, I don't feel good about this.
갑자기 멈추지 마!
Don't stop so suddenly!
뭐, 뭔가 빛났어.
S- something gleamed.
온다!
It's coming!
도, 도망쳐!
R- run away!
어?
Huh?
자, 잠깐!
W- wait for us!
이거 꽤 재미있네! 사람을 놀래킨다는 거.작전 2 성공. 이와노이, 네게 넘길게.
Surprising people is pretty fun! Operation 2 successful. Iwanoi, your turn.
OK.
기다려!
Wait!
잇키!
Ikki!
잡았다! 혼자서 도망치지 마!
I got you! Don't run away only by yourself!
야, 왜 그래, 잇키?
Hey, what's wrong, Ikki?
저, 저거.
T- that.
블루즈독, 이제 됐어.
Bluesdog, we're good.
그거 무섭네. 하고 있는 나도 무서워...
That's scary. Even I'm scared when I'm doing this...
역시 무서워!
It really is scary!
이제 겁난다. 좀 지렸다.
I'm scared. I wet myself!
따라오지는 않는 거 같아.
It seems that they're not chasing us.
있잖아, 왜 우리가 이렇게 된 거야?
Hey, why are we in this situation?
알까보냐!
Like hell I know!
이, 이번엔 뭐야?!
W- what is it this time?1
키, 키쿠히메?
K- Kikuhime?
진짜! 이제 알겠다!
Damn! I get it now!
아, 아리카!
A- Arika!
잠깐, 키쿠히메! 네가 한 짓이었구나!
Hey, Kikuhime! You did all of this!
여기 봐!
Look at me!
나왔다!
It's there!
이, 이번엔 뭐야?!
W- what is it this time?!
잠깐. 저거 메다로트잖아?
Wait. Isn't that a Medarot?
페퍼캣! 왜 여기에?
Peppercat! Why are you here?
아니, 뭔가 모습이 이상해.
Stop. She doesn't look right.
페퍼캣!
Peppercat!
안 돼!
Stop!
뭔 짓이야, 페퍼캣!
What are you doing, Peppercat?!
메타비! 바리스터 준비해!
Metabee, prepare Ballister!
좋아!
Got it!
부탁이야! 페퍼캣 쏘지 마!
Please! Don't shoot Peppercat!
키쿠히메?
Kikuhime?
지금 얘 병에 걸렸어!
She's sick right now!
병?
Sick?
그렇구나. 뭔가 사정이 있어 보이네.
I see. You have a story.
그, 그게...
T- that's...
브라스! 너까지!
Brass! Even you!
어째, 잇키! 공격할까?
What should we do, Ikki? Are we attacking?
안 돼! 브라스는 어떤 죄도 없어!
No! Brass did nothing wrong!
그래도 이대로는 우리가 당해!
But at this rate we're gonna be done for!
안 돼! 아픈 메다로트하고 로보틀한다니!
No! You can't have a Robattle against sick Medarots!
그럼 어쩌란 거야!
Then what should I do?!
이렇게 되면 어쩔 수 없지!
We have only one choice!
도망쳐!
Run!
-역시.
-잠깐!
-I knew it.
-Wait for us!
과학실
Science Room
이 정도 있으면 안심이야!
That will keep us safe!
그러고 보니 이거 뭐야?
By the way, what's this?
몰라?
Don't you know?
서, 설마, 이거...
C- could this be...
뭐?
What?
관. (히쯔기)
A coffin. (Hitsugi)
뭐야, 그렇구나!
Oh, I see now!
그 관이 뭐야?
Hey, what's coffin?
하얗고, 털이 더부룩하고, 메헤헤헤 하고 울고.
It's white, full of hair, and cry like, baaaaaaa.
아, 그거구나!
Oh, I see now!
양(히쯔지) 말고 관(히쯔기)! 죽은 사람 넣는 상자 말야!
Not sheep (Hitsuji)! It's coffin (Hitsugi)! The box where dead people are put in!
죽은 사람...
Dead people...
뭐, 뭐?!
W- what?!
뭐, 뭐뭐, 뭐야, 이거?!
W- wha- what's this?!
드라큘라 메다로트?
Dracula Medarot?
잇키 군 잘 왔어. 감사하지.
Ikki, welcome. Thank you for showing up.
뭐, 뭐야?!
W- what did you say?!
자, 여기부터는 차분히 내 돈 드라큘리오가 상대해 줄 거야.
From now on, my Don Draculio will face you carefully.
잠깐, 너구나! 모두의 메다로트에게 이상한 병 감염시킨 거!
So it was you who infected everyone's Medarots with some weird disease!
흥! 유령엔 약해도 로보틀에선 안 져!
Hmph! While I might be weak to ghosts, I do not lose in Robattles!
그건 어떨까. 가라, 돈 드라큐리오! 놈들을 네 새로운 종으로 만들어라!
We'll see about that. Go, Don Draculio! Make them into your new slaves!
가자, 메타비!
Let's do this, Metabee!
좋아!
Right!
블래스터 발사!
Blasters, fire!
이게!
Damn you!
젠장! 블래스터가 안 먹어!
Damn! Blaster isn't working!
퓨저 발사!
Fuser, fire!
저 근거리에서 피해가 없다니!
He's not damaged in that point-blank range?!
쓸모없는 저항은 관둬.
Give up with that futile resistance.
메타비! 괜찮아?!
Metabee! Are you okay?!
빡친다!
I'm mad now!
왜 그래, 메타비!
What's wrong, Metabee?!
너야말로 제대로 된 지시를 내려 봐!
Make some good instructions!
그렇지! 드라큘라의 약점이라면 이거지!
That's it! Dracula's weakness is this!
그래! 먼 옛날부터의 약속! 드라큘라 퇴치에는 양파지!
Yes! It's a promise from a long time ago! Onions work well to eradicate Dracula!
악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산
Evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal
야! 그딴 거 메다로트한테 안 먹혀!
Hey! That's no way going to work to Medarots!
-뭐, 뭐?!
-그럼 이거야!
-W- what?!
-Then this will do!
악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산, 악령 퇴산
Evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal evil spirit dispersal
이제 졌겠지! 드라큘라에게는 십자가가! 이거야말로 누구나 아는 약속이야!
Now you should be lost! This cross always work against Dracula! That is a promise that everyone knows about!
니들 진짜!
You idiots!
어? 이것도야?
What? That didn't work too?
그럼 이건?
Then what about this?
이건?
How's this?
And this?
이건?
This?
지금이야!
Now!
돈 드라큐리오!
Don Draculio!
먹힌다! 다시 한 번!
It's working! Do it again!
안 빠져!
I can't get it off me!
잘한다! 그대로 팔을 비틀어버려!
Good job! Twist his arms like that!
젠장! 어째, 잇키!
Damn! What should I do now, Ikki?!
잇키!
Ikki!
메타비! 양팔을 떼어버려!
Metabee! Take your both arms off!
뭐?!
What?!
바리스터 발사 준비!
Ballister, prepare to fire!
어쩔래, 더 할래?
Up for more fight?
모두의 메다로트를 좀비같이 만들고, 그런 식으로 싸우고, 부끄럽지도 않냐?
You made everyone's Medarots like zombies, and fought in such a dirty way. Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
메다로트가 불쌍하다고 생각 안 해?
Have you ever thought those Medarots are pitiful?
돈 드라큘리오...
Dom Draculio...
알겠어. 내가 졌어. 돈 드라큐리오, 전투 정지.
I get it. I lost. Don Draculio, cease fighting.
위험했어...
That was close...
잇키.
Ikki.
그래.
Yeah.
다행이네. 좋은 마스터가 있어서.
Good for you. You have a good master.
어? 이건 데스 메다로트가 아니잖아!
Huh? This isn't a Death Medarot!
그런데 왜 이렇게...
But why?
사실은 코쿠류 씨에게...
To tell you the truth, Mr. Kokuryu did this...
코쿠류?
Kokuryu?!
돈 드라큐리오를 누구에게도 지지 않는 최고의 머신으로 만들어 준대서...
He said that he'll make Don Draculio into a matchless machine that will defeat everybody.
그래서 내 소중한 브라스나 모두의 소중한 메다로트를 좀비로 만들어도 된다는 거야?!
So is that a valid reason to make my precious Brass or everyone's Medarots into zombies?!
빠, 빨리! 그 병 치료하는 백신을!
H- hurry! That vaccine!
이걸 뿌리면 병은 낫습니다.
If you spray this, their disease will go away.
이렇게 해피 엔딩은 안 돼. 난 그렇게 쉽지 않아.
I can't let this end with a happy ending. I am not that easy.
가라, 키리킨자무!
Go, Kirikinzamu!
KKZ형 키리킨자무
KKZ Type Kirikinzam
좋아, 거기야!
Right, that's it!
뭐야, 함정이냐!
Was that a trap?!
돈 드라큘리오!
Don Draculio!
잇키, 나도 싸울래! 어서 백신을!
Ikki! I'll fight too! Hurry up with that vaccine!
그래! 간다!
Right! Here it goes!
야옹.
Meow.
페퍼캣.
Peppercat.
야옹!
Meow!
-두목! 여긴 어디에요?
-페퍼캣!
-Boss! Where are we?
-Peppercat!
잘도 내 소중한 페퍼캣을!
How dare you do that to my dear Peppercat?!
이와노이, 카가미야마! 죽을 각오로 가자!
Iwanoi and Kagamiyama! Deal with them to your death!
예!
Roger!
브라스, 오늘은 되는 만큼 날뛰어!
Brass! You can rage as much as you wanted today!
텐료 잇키. 승부는 보류한다.
Tenryo Ikki. The match will be postponed.
멈춰, 코쿠류!
Stop right there, Kokuryu!
내, 내 돈 드라큘리오...
M- my Don Draculio...
마스터...
Master...
돈 드라큘리오?!
Don Draculio?!
아직 완전히 부서진 건 아니야.
He's not completely broken.
나에 씨한테 가면 괜찮아질 거야.
If you go meet Ms. Nae, then he'll be fine.
나에 씨?
Ms. Nae?
있어. 어떤 고장도 고쳐 주는 메다로트 수리 천재야.
Well, she's a genius of repairing Medarots!
좋아.
Good.
어때요?
How's him?
왼쪽의 칼 상처가 틴펫까지 닿아서...
Injury from sword on left has damaged the Tinpet too.
괜찮을까요?
Will he be fine?
잠깐만.
Wait a moment.
돈 드라큘리오.
Don Draculio.
이제 될 거야!
That'll do!
수리 끝났어요?
Is the repair done?
끝났어.
It's done.
그래서 어때요?
So, how is him?
자, 내려와.
You can come down.
네!
Got it!
돈 드라큘리오! 너!
Don Draculio! Hey!
-대단해!
-반짝반짝!
-Awesome!
-Shiny!
상처가 눈에 띄지 않게 새로 칠했어.
I painted again so that injury won't be visible.
가, 감사합니다!
T- thank you so much!
그치, 돈 드라큘리오?
Right, Don Draculio?
예!
Yeah!
잘 됐네, 잘 됐어! 나도 그렇게 다시 칠해지면 좋겠어!
Good for you! I want to be painted again like you!
뭔 소리야. 아, 내가 다시 칠해 줄게.
What are you talking about? Oh, I'll paint you again!
싫어! 나에 씨가 좋아!
No way! I like Ms. Nae's painting!
뭐야, 그게 어디 있어! 가만히 있어!
Hey, what's so bad about mine? Stay put!
-나에 씨가 좋아!
-나도 괜찮아!
-I like Ms. Nae!
-I'm good enough too!
그만해! 그만! 그만해! 싫어!
Stop it! Stop! Stop it! Nooo!
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
인기 프로그램, 돌격 아이들 쇼에 출연하게 된 잇키와 메타비.
Ikki and Metabee are taking part in Rush Idol Show.
귀여운 사회자 누나들에게 둘러싸여 둘의 토크가 최고조에 달했다.
Surrounded by cute hostesses, their talk was in midst of the climax.
그 와중 돌연 나타난 긴카이와 잠수함형 데스 메다로트 네시지에게 잇키는 문답무용의 로보틀에 말려든다.
During that, Ginkai and submarine type Death Medarot, Nessage forces Ikki into a no-question-asked Robattle.
과연 로보틀의 결과는 어떻게?
What will be the outcome of Robattle?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 풀에서 로보틀!
Next time on Medarot Damashii! Robattle in Pool!
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!